It's done!
Hello!
Today...
Oh! It's heavy!
I'm going to make a campfire
I'm going to make a bamboo fire!
I'm carrying it now.
It's very heavy.
Hang in there!
Here we are!
The sea!
It's so sunny today, isn't it?
Yes! So...
I have a lot of luggage.
I'm including my luggage today.
Let's pull it out.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Wow!
I'm off!
Ha! It's heavy!
Here.
It's done!
Like this
chair
So cute!
I bought this one.
It's a chair that you pull
It's a puller.
I bought a chair, too.
Here we go.
This is a bamboo fire.
This is...
It's a Snow Peak.
This is a Snow Peak bamboo fire pit.
Let's light it.
It's lit.
It's lit!
One channel
Ta-da!
Now...
This house
Today
We are going to cook some meat.
Ta-da!
No.
Let's open it.
Oh, I'll get the fire going.
It's about time.
Hot!
Bon appétit!
I think it's on fire.
Hey! Sorry.
Yum!
Ha-ha-ha!
Looks delicious!
It's good.
Just a little more.
Red one.
Ooh.
Oh!
Bon appétit.
Whew!
Yum.
Delicious!
Ta-da!
Popcorn!
Put the syrup in.
Watch this.
Let's try it.
It's a little burnt.
Whew.
Burnt.
Looks delicious.
I'm gonna gain so much weight today.
Next time.
Looks so good!
Yum!
Now, Kitakata...
I'm going to make Fukushima meat!
I'm going to make it!
Looks delicious!
Guru guru at a time!
Looks so good!
Ta-da!
Thank you so much!
Yummy.
Yummmm.
Delicious!
It's so good!
Hot!
One channel
Ta-da!
A little more fire goes out
Now it's fine.
Even in this state
It's so warm!It's so warm.
The fire fell out, but...
It's so beautiful.
It's getting cold
It's getting colder
My hands and feet are warm
Thank you for watching